afghan123.com 2019-03-21

# Our Privacy Policy - Afghan123

**What information do we collect?**   
We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. 

When contacting us or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, phone number or country.

 **What do we use your information for?**   
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

1\. To personalize your experience  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.

2\. To process request  
We use your device type, operating system and browser information to deliver specific content to you. 

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of service requested. 

**Do we use cookies?**   
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your web browser) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**   
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**   
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Terms and Conditions**   
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <https://www.afghan123.com/terms-of-service/>

**Your Consent**   
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 2015-02-08

**Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

https://www.afghan123.com
